export const questionSectionData = [
  {
    question: "What is the total Andromeda supply ?",
    response: "There is a total of 2061 unique Andromeda collectible NFT."
  },
  {
    question: "What is the mint limit per wallet ?",
    response:
      "The maximum is fixed to 5 NFT per wallet during both pre-sales and public mint stages. "
  },
  {
    question: "What will be the price ?",
    response:
      "One NFT will cost 0.03ETH during the Pre-sales phase. For the public mint, price is set to 0.05ETH."
  },
  {
    question: "When will be the mint ?",
    response:
      "Pre-mint will be 15th Octobre 12:00 CET. Public mint will be 18th Octobre 12:00 CET."
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy Andromeda ?",
    response:
      "You can only acquired Andromeda from our website (https://planet61nft.com). Connect your wallet to have acces to the mint button."
  },
  {
    question: "How to be part on the whitelist ?",
    response:
      "We decided to work under Ehereum blockain and the market place is Opensea."
  },
  {
    question: "When Andromeda will be launched on second marketplace?",
    response:
      "The reveal and the publication on the second marketplace will be when 100% of the collection will be sold."
  },
  {
    question: "Why Andromeda is unique?",
    response:
      "The project is unique because it combines art and technology in the service of people and the community is the heart of the project. "
  },
  {
    question: "What are the utility to hold Andromeda?",
    response:
      "You are participating in the creation of a community and a new world. Through your support, you also enable the development of many environmental projects on the planet earth. The access to the community and to the NFTs allows you to live unforgettable moments thanks to the gifts that will be offered periodically. "
  },
  {
    question: "What will be the royalty rate on second market?",
    response:
      "10%. The budget will be dedicated to marketing and developmment purpose, saving planet actions and gifts for our community."
  },
  {
    question: "How to win Andormeda clothes and prizes?",
    response:
      "We will periodically raffle for winners. The incredible principal price will be awarded when 100% of the NFTs have been sold. Owners of NFT will be contacted in our Discord and the team will take contact to manage the shipping."
  },
  {
    question: "How to contact the Teams?",
    response:
      "Use our different media such as Twitter, Discord or send us mail to : planet61nft@gmail.com"
  }
];
